const qna = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'Where is the wedding taking place?',
    answer: 'Lagos Nigeria, you can find out more on the Venue page.',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'Is there a reception venue?',
    answer: 'There is no reception.',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'Will refreshment be provided?',
    answer: 'Yes, food and drinks will be available for everyone.',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'What is the dresscode?',
    answer:
      "There is no formal dress code, so feel free to wear whatever you want. You can choose a color from the color palette on the homepage if you'd like. The main thing is to wear something you feel comfortable and happy in.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'Can I come even though I was not invited?',
    answer:
      'If you did not receive a formal invitation, please do not attend the in-person event as space is limited. However, you are welcome to join via Zoom - the Zoom details will be provided 3 days before the wedding date. This way you can still participate remotely if an invitation was not sent to you for the physical venue.',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `I can't attend the wedding in person. Will there be a virtual wedding celebration?`,
    answer:
      'Yes, there will be a virtual wedding celebration. Zoom details will be provided three days before the wedding day, allowing you to attend remotely.',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'I canâ€™t locate the venue, who can I call?',
    answer: `If you have trouble finding the wedding venue, you can call  +2348121497473 or +2347030251131  for assistance and directions. Don't hesitate to reach out to that number if you get lost or need help locating the site. Help is available to make sure you can find your way there without any issues.`,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'Is there parking available in your wedding venue?',
    answer: 'Yes, there is sufficient parking available at the wedding venue.',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'Have you reserved blocks of rooms at one or more hotels?',
    answer: `No, we have not reserved blocks of rooms at any hotels. However, there are several affordable hotels in the Ikeja axis that you can consider for accommodation during the wedding.`,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `I'm visiting from out of town. What can I do while I'm in Lagos?`,
    answer: ` While visiting Lagos, Nigeria, there are several activities and attractions that you can explore to make the most of your trip before and after the wedding. Here are some suggestions:`,
    details: [
      ' Visit Lekki Conservation Centre: This nature reserve offers a refreshing escape from the bustling city. You can enjoy a walk on the canopy walkway, spot wildlife, and explore the lush greenery.',
      'Take a boat ride to Tarkwa Bay: Located off the coast of Lagos, Tarkwa Bay is a beautiful beach destination. You can enjoy swimming, sunbathing, and even engage in water sports like jet skiing or snorkeling.',
      'Visit Nike Art Gallery: This renowned art gallery in Lekki showcases a vast collection of Nigerian art, including paintings, sculptures, and textiles. You can appreciate the creativity and talent of local artists.',
      'Explore the vibrant markets: Lagos is known for its bustling markets. From the popular Balogun Market to the artsy Lekki Arts and Crafts Market, you can immerse yourself in the vibrant atmosphere, shop for traditional crafts, fabrics, and try local street food',
      'Enjoy the nightlife: Lagos has a thriving nightlife scene with numerous clubs, bars, and restaurants. You can experience the energetic music and dance culture, enjoy live performances, or indulge in delicious Nigerian cuisine.',
      'Remember to also experience the local cuisine, try traditional dishes like jollof rice, suya (grilled meat), and puff puff (a popular snack). Lagos offers a blend of cultural experiences, natural beauty, and vibrant city life, ensuring an exciting and memorable visit.',
    ],
  },
];

export default qna;
